CURRICULUM VITAE

Pham Ngoc Huy (Robert Pham)

Web Developer

Phone: +0359221014 (VN)

Email: huysanti123456@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/robert-pahm/

SUMMARY

I'm a fullstack developer with 1 year of experience in Laravel (PHP) technology with good knowledge of OOP, Database Design and Design Patterns.

Learning new languages and technologies is what I am passionate about. I am regarded as a thoughtful leader because I like to help and motivate others and tend to work well within the group.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Languages:
 - PHP, Javascript, Java
 - HTML5, CSS3, Responsive
- Frameworks/Platforms:
 - ReactJS. VueJS
 - Webpack, Babel, ES6
 - Laravel, PHP MVC, WebAPI
 - Jquery, Bootstrap, Ant Design,
 - Linux
- Database Management Systems:
 - MySQL, MongoDB
- · Others:
 - Good understanding of OOP methodologies
 - Setting up CI/CD pipelines, using Docker and hands-on with Cloud Platform: AWS

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

- Version Control :
 - Git, SVN
- Foreign Languages:

English:

- IELTS: 6.5
- Soft Skills:
 - Teamwork
 - Time management
 - Business communication

CURRICULUM VITAE

HEADPHONES E-COMMERCE WEBSITE (VN)

From 06//2022 to 09/2022

Position : FullStack Developer

 Description: A web app used by the RAXZ company to manage orders, drivers, customer booking for selling headphones, and more.

Link github:

https://github.com/JustAbusiness/Group-37--FULLSTACK-WEB-APPLICATIONS

• Teamsize: 4

Technologies:

+ Legacy front-end project : VueJS + Bootstrap 4

+ Backend : Laravel, MySQL

• Responsibilities:

- + Based on the demands from stakeholders, create the UX/UI and put the solution (both front-end and back-end) into practice.
- + Design database schema and implement back-end services.
- + Work together with the team leader to establish and enhance the workflow of the team.

ONLINE GAME PLATFORM (VN)

From 10/2022 to 01/2023

- Position: Full Stack Developer
- Description: 2HKT is a digital marketplace that distributes PC games. After purchasing PC games, customers may install them online directly to their cloud storage using the 2HKT software.
- Link github: https://github.com/bits-hkt2/gamestore-hkt2

Teamsize: 5

- Technologies:
 - + Front end: VueJS, Bootstrap 4, Ant-Design

CURRICULUM VITAE

- + Back end : Laravel (PHP), PhpMyAdmin (Maria DB)
- Responsibilities:
 - + Develop and fix the application's defect base on requirements
 - + Develop small modules of the system
 - + Prepare materials and a technical guide for developers who will be joining the project in the middle.

EDUCATION

RMIT University (Vietnam) 10/2021 - Now

- Studying Information Technology Minor: Web Development
- Bachelor IT Degree